{
    "cards" : [
        {
            "front": "I",
            "back": "Yo"
        },
        {
            "front": "you",
            "back": "tu"
        },
        {
            "front": "he",
            "back": "el"
        },
        {
            "front": "she",
            "back": "ella"
        },
        {
            "front": "we/us",
            "back": "nosotros/nosotras"
        }, 
        {
            "front": "hello",
            "back": "hola"
        },
        {
            "front": "you (formal)",
            "back": "usted"
        },
        {
            "front": "work",
            "back": "trabajo"
        },
        {
            "front": "Accounting",
            "back": "Contabilidad"
        },
        {
            "front": "Computer",
            "back": "Computadora"
        },
        {
            "front": "shoes",
            "back": "zapatos"
        }
    ]
}